<conversation entryNode="0" requirePause="true">
  <node index="0" character ="FriendBot">
    <prompt>Ah, you've arrived! Excellent!
Long distance cryo travel can be disorientating and I'm sure you've got a lot of questions, so give a tap on my panel and I'll take you through everything you need to know!</prompt>
    <continue target ="1"/>
  </node>
  <node index ="1" character ="FriendBot">
    <prompt>Welcome to your exciting future in the criminal rehabilitation program!</prompt>
    <continue target="2"/>
  </node>
  <node index ="2" character ="FriendBot">
    <prompt>But I don't need to tell you that, you're the filthy criminal, you know what horrifying thing you did!</prompt>
    <continue target ="3"/>
  </node>
  <node index ="3" character ="FriendBot">
    <prompt>Not to worry though, I am your F.R.I.E.N.D!
As your F.R.I.E.N.D I am both responsible for you, and responsible for deeming when you will be fit to return to society!</prompt>
    <continue target ="5"/>
  </node>
  <node index ="5" character ="FriendBot">
    <prompt>Now criminal, your exciting life as a galaxy rim asteroid miner can begin!</prompt>
    <continue target ="6"/>
  </node>
  <node index ="6" character ="FriendBot">
    <prompt>Your job is to mine flux crystals and other useful minerals for the grand empire, then take them back to your mining station. Shouldn't be too hard right?</prompt>
    <continue target ="7"/>
  </node>
  <node index ="7" character ="FriendBot">
    <prompt>Also it is suggested that you aim to gather some ice while you're out'n'about... 
Only if you value the ability to breathe of course!</prompt>
    <continue target ="8"/>
  </node>
  <node index ="8" character ="FriendBot">
    <prompt>You'll notice of course that your oxygen supply is limited, so don't fly too far from the station! Go get 'em kid!
Press W to accelerate, and S to slow down, click anywhere to laser it, and try not to fly into anything...    
    </prompt>
    <continue target ="9"/>
  </node>
  <node index ="9" character ="FriendBot">
    <prompt>Any questions before we get started?</prompt>
    <response target ="14">No Sir! I am a model citizen of the empire and will do my duty in recompence for the crime I committed!</response>
    <response target ="10">Uh... yeah... would you mind telling me why I'm here?</response>
    <response target ="11">What the hell does 'F.R.I.E.N.D' stand for?</response>
    <response target ="12">Screw you! Let me go!</response>
  </node>
  <node index ="10" character ="FriendBot">
    <prompt>Of course not silly! All criminals have their memories erased so they can begin their life anew!</prompt>
    <continue target ="9"/>
  </node>
  <node index ="11" character ="FriendBot">
    <prompt>Don't worry about such silly things!
Just remember that I'm your F.R.I.E.N.D!</prompt>
    <continue target ="9"/>
  </node>
  <node index ="12" character ="FriendBot">
    <prompt>I have to warn you criminal that for every transgression against our code you will receive
*** 8 DAYS *** added to your sentence.
Maybe you just like working for the empire though, such a good citizen!</prompt>
    <continue target ="13"/>
  </node>
  <node index ="13" character ="FriendBot">
    <prompt>F.R.I.E.N.D proceeds to read you the criminal code of conduct... it's very boring...</prompt>
    <continue target ="9"/>
  </node>
  <node index ="14" character ="FriendBot">
    <prompt>Well done, do try to do a good job now criminal!</prompt>
    <continue target ="-1"/>
  </node>
</conversation>