<conversation entryNode="0" requirePause="true">
  <node index="0" character ="FriendBot2">
    <prompt>I am being compelled by my new programming to congratulate you on destroying that Imperial striker...</prompt>
    <continue target ="1"/>
  </node>
  <node index="1" character ="FriendBot2">
    <prompt>I have also been reliably informed by this programming that I am, in fact, stored locally inside a chip in your brain...
This doesn't bode well for me if you explode so do me a favour and stay alive for now?
    </prompt>
    <continue target="2"/>
  </node>
  <node index="2" character ="FriendBot2">
    <prompt>This is all highly, highly irregular... Do you have any questions I might be able to answer?</prompt>
    <response target="4">What the hell is going on? I don't even know who the empire are, let alone the rebels!</response>
    <response target="5">Where do we go now?</response>
    <response target="6">What. The. Hell. Does F.R.I.E.N.D stand for?</response>
  </node>
  <node index="3" character ="FriendBot2">
    <prompt>Did you have any other questions?</prompt>
    <response target="4">What the hell is going on? I don't even know who the empire are, let alone the rebels!</response>
    <response target="5">Where do we go now?</response>
    <response target="6">What. The. Hell. Does F.R.I.E.N.D stand for?</response>
    <response target="7">No, I guess that's everything...</response>
  </node>
  <node index="4" character="FriendBot2">
    <prompt>Ah, that's a side effect of the memory erasure I'm afraid. The empire are the oldest civilisation in the galaxy (by their account). The rebels are... well rebels... I guess?</prompt>
    <continue target="3"/>
  </node>
  <node index="5" character="FriendBot2">
    <prompt>Well I've received some coordinates from these rebels... they're pointing us in a rather alarming direction though I'm afraid...</prompt>
    <continue target="3"/>
  </node>
  <node index="6" character="FriendBot2">
    <prompt>Ahhhh that old chestnut. I believe it stands for Forced Rehabilitiation Incubator and Enforcement Neurological Device
Funny that I didn't know that before now ey? I'm literally inside your head!</prompt>
    <continue target="3"/>
  </node>
  <node index="7" character="FriendBot2">
    <prompt>Right, so the coordinates the "rebels" mentioned seem to point somewhere in the dead sector... that's... alarming.
Nothing but pirates and scrap metal out there. It's the site of a very old war, which I suppose you've forgotten.</prompt>
    <continue target="8"/>
  </node>
  <node index="8" character="FriendBot2">
    <prompt>I'm afraid there's nothing for it... I'll add the dead sector coordinates to your galaxy map.
We don't have an exact coordinate, so we'll have to jump then I'll try and point you in the direction of the signal source...
Expect to encounter a lot of hostiles, I suggest you try and craft some improved weaponry before we make the jump.</prompt>
    <continue target="9"/>
  </node>
  <node index="9" character="FriendBot2">
    <prompt>Well... good luck I guess?
Friend out?</prompt>
    <continue target="-1"/>
  </node>
</conversation>